myflashstore.net 2015-03-17

# Privacy Policy - myFlashStore.net

myFlashStore is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains our data processing practices and your options regarding the ways in which your personal data is used. If you have any requests concerning your personal information or any queries with regard to our processing please contact us at  [support@myflashstore.net](mailto:support@myflashstore.net).

###  Information collected

myFlashStore collects the details provided by you on registration, and the transaction information to provide you with your order history.

We may collect additional information in connection with your participation in any promotions or competitions offered by us and information you provide when giving us feedback or completing profile forms. We also monitor customer traffic patterns and site use which enables us to improve the service we provide.

###  Use of your information and your preferences

We will use your contact details only to communicate with you. We may use your information to send you offers and news about myFlashStore products and services or those of other carefully selected companies which we think may be of interest to you. We may contact you by email.

Once you have registered to use myFlashStore.net, you will be provided with access to a "User Details" page that will allow you to edit your contact details.

We like to hear your views to help us improve our service. From time to time, we may contact you by email to ask your opinions.

We may use your information to verify your identity and prevent or detect fraud. In performing these checks your information may be disclosed to credit reference agencies, who may keep a record of that information. This is not a credit check and your credit rating will be unaffected.

Please note that there may be instances where it may be necessary for us to communicate with you, in any event, for administrative or operational reasons relating to our service.

###  Disclosures of your information

Your information will only be used by myFlashStore companies. We will never pass your personal information to anyone else, except where we are required or permitted to do so by law, for any successors in title to our business and suppliers that process information on our behalf both in the UK and abroad. We may also use and disclose information in aggregate (so that no individual customers are identified) for marketing and strategic development purposes.

###  Other web sites

Our web site may contain links to other web sites which are outside our control and are not covered by this Privacy Policy. If you access other sites using the links provided, the operators of these sites may collect information from you which will be used by them in accordance with their privacy policy, which may differ from ours.

###  Cookies

"Cookies" are small pieces of information sent by a web server to a web browser, which enables the server to collect information from the browser. You can find out more about the way cookies work on [http://www.cookiecentral.com](http://www.cookiecentral.com/). myFlashStore uses cookies for a number of purposes, for instance to enable us to simplify the logging on process for registered users, to help ensure the security and authenticity of registered users, and to enable traffic monitoring.

Non-registered visitors of the site are sent anonymous cookies to keep track of their browsing patterns and build up a demographic profile. In addition, any visitor who has clicked on a myFlashStore.net advertisement on another site that links to myFlashStore.net will be sent anonymous cookies that will allow us to analyse advertising effectiveness and manage our relationship with affiliate sites.

Whilst you do not need to allow your browser to accept cookies in order to browse much of our web site or to access many of our services, you must have cookies enabled to use certain parts of the service or access any areas reserved for registered users.

Most browsers allow you to turn off the cookie function. If you want to know how to do this please look at the help menu on your browser. As described above this will restrict the online myFlashStore services you can use.
